question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "The first televised presidential debate was between Jimmy Carter and Gerald Ford.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "The Hundred Years War was fought for more than a hundred years.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "Adolf Hitler was tried at the Nuremberg trials.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "Oxford University is older than the Aztec Empire. ",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "The French Kingdom helped the United States gain their independence over Great Britain during the Revolutionary War.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "United States President Ronald Reagan was the first president to appoint a woman to the Supreme Court. ",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "If you grab the bladed end of a longsword in a specific way, you will not cut yourself.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "Japan was part of the Allied Powers during World War I.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "Assyrian king Sennacherib&#039;s destruction of Babylon in 689 BCE was viewed as a triumph by other Assyrian citizens.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "category": "History",
        "question": "The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]
